const bibleBooks = [
    { front: 'Genesis', back: 'Revelation Genesis Exodus' },
    { front: 'Exodus', back: 'Genesis Exodus Leviticus' },
    { front: 'Leviticus', back: 'Exodus Leviticus Numbers' },
    { front: 'Numbers', back: 'Leviticus Numbers Deuteronomy' },
    { front: 'Deuteronomy', back: 'Numbers Deuteronomy Joshua' },
    { front: 'Joshua', back: 'Deuteronomy Joshua Judges' },
    { front: 'Judges', back: 'Joshua Judges Ruth' },
    { front: 'Ruth', back: 'Judges Ruth 1 Samuel' },
    { front: '1 Samuel', back: 'Ruth 1 Samuel 2 Samuel' },
    { front: '2 Samuel', back: '1 Samuel 2 Samuel 1 Kings' },
    { front: '1 Kings', back: '2 Samuel 1 Kings 2 Kings' },
    { front: '2 Kings', back: '1 Kings 2 Kings 1 Chronicles' },
    { front: '1 Chronicles', back: '2 Kings 1 Chronicles 2 Chronicles' },
    { front: '2 Chronicles', back: '1 Chronicles 2 Chronicles Ezra' },
    { front: 'Ezra', back: '2 Chronicles Ezra Nehemiah' },
    { front: 'Nehemiah', back: 'Ezra Nehemiah Esther' },
    { front: 'Esther', back: 'Nehemiah Esther Job' },
    { front: 'Job', back: 'Esther Job Psalms' },
    { front: 'Psalms', back: 'Job Psalms Proverbs' },
    { front: 'Proverbs', back: 'Psalms Proverbs Ecclesiastes' },
    { front: 'Ecclesiastes', back: 'Proverbs Ecclesiastes Song of Solomon' },
    { front: 'Song of Solomon', back: 'Ecclesiastes Song of Solomon Isaiah' },
    { front: 'Isaiah', back: 'Song of Solomon Isaiah Jeremiah' },
    { front: 'Jeremiah', back: 'Isaiah Jeremiah Lamentations' },
    { front: 'Lamentations', back: 'Jeremiah Lamentations Ezekiel' },
    { front: 'Ezekiel', back: 'Lamentations Ezekiel Daniel' },
    { front: 'Daniel', back: 'Ezekiel Daniel Hosea' },
    { front: 'Hosea', back: 'Daniel Hosea Joel' },
    { front: 'Joel', back: 'Hosea Joel Amos' },
    { front: 'Amos', back: 'Joel Amos Obadiah' },
    { front: 'Obadiah', back: 'Amos Obadiah Jonah' },
    { front: 'Jonah', back: 'Obadiah Jonah Micah' },
    { front: 'Micah', back: 'Jonah Micah Nahum' },
    { front: 'Nahum', back: 'Micah Nahum Habakkuk' },
    { front: 'Habakkuk', back: 'Nahum Habakkuk Zephaniah' },
    { front: 'Zephaniah', back: 'Habakkuk Zephaniah Haggai' },
    { front: 'Haggai', back: 'Zephaniah Haggai Zechariah' },
    { front: 'Zechariah', back: 'Haggai Zechariah Malachi' },
    { front: 'Malachi', back: 'Zechariah Malachi Matthew' },
    { front: 'Matthew', back: 'Malachi Matthew Mark' },
    { front: 'Mark', back: 'Matthew Mark Luke' },
    { front: 'Luke', back: 'Mark Luke John' },
    { front: 'John', back: 'Luke John Acts' },
    { front: 'Acts', back: 'John Acts Romans' },
    { front: 'Romans', back: 'Acts Romans 1 Corinthians' },
    { front: '1 Corinthians', back: 'Romans 1 Corinthians 2 Corinthians' },
    { front: '2 Corinthians', back: '1 Corinthians 2 Corinthians Galatians' },
    { front: 'Galatians', back: '2 Corinthians Galatians Ephesians' },
    { front: 'Ephesians', back: 'Galatians Ephesians Philippians' },
    { front: 'Philippians', back: 'Ephesians Philippians Colossians' },
    { front: 'Colossians', back: 'Philippians Colossians 1 Thessalonians' },
    { front: '1 Thessalonians', back: 'Colossians 1 Thessalonians 2 Thessalonians' },
    { front: '2 Thessalonians', back: '1 Thessalonians 2 Thessalonians 1 Timothy' },
    { front: '1 Timothy', back: '2 Thessalonians 1 Timothy 2 Timothy' },
    { front: '2 Timothy', back: '1 Timothy 2 Timothy Titus' },
    { front: 'Titus', back: '2 Timothy Titus Philemon' },
    { front: 'Philemon', back: 'Titus Philemon Hebrews' },
    { front: 'Hebrews', back: 'Philemon Hebrews James' },
    { front: 'James', back: 'Hebrews James 1 Peter' },
    { front: '1 Peter', back: 'James 1 Peter 2 Peter' },
    { front: '2 Peter', back: '1 Peter 2 Peter 1 John' },
    { front: '1 John', back: '2 Peter 1 John 2 John' },
    { front: '2 John', back: '1 John 2 John 3 John' },
    { front: '3 John', back: '2 John 3 John Jude' },
    { front: 'Jude', back: '3 John Jude Revelation' },
    { front: 'Revelation', back: 'Jude Revelation Genesis' }
];

export default bibleBooks;